var questions = {
    Q1: {
        question: "What was the Full name of Moses' sister?",
        a: "A. Naamah",
        b: "B. Phoebe",
        c: "C. Miriam",
        d: "D. Jemima",
        correctAnswer: "C. Miriam"
    },
    Q2: {
        question: "What did the children of Israel call the bread? (Exodus 16:15)",
        a: "A. Onani",
        b: "B. Manna",
        c: "C. Kafesh",
        d: "D. Rama",
        correctAnswer: "B. Manna"
    },
    Q3: {
        question: "What brought forth water when Moses struck it? (Exodus 17:6)",
        a: "A. A pit",
        b: "B. A rock",
        c: "C. A tree",
        d: "D. A pot",
        correctAnswer: "B. A rock"
    },
    Q4: {
        question: "Which woman of the Bible was the world's first mother?",
        a: "A. Jezebel",
        b: "B. Eve",
        c: "C. Gaea",
        d: "D. Sarah",
        correctAnswer: "B. Eve"
    },

    Q5: {
        question: "What was the name of Sarah's son? (Genesis 17:19)",
        a: "A. Jacob",
        b: "B. Abraham",
        c: "C. Isaac",
        d: "D. Ishmael",
        correctAnswer: "C. Isaac"
    },
    Q6: {
        question: "Who married Moses?",
        a: "A. Zipporah",
        b: "B. Phoebe",
        c: "C. Zilpah",
        d: "D. Susanna",
        correctAnswer: "A. Zipporah"
    },
    Q7: {
        question: "Whom did Abram marry? (Genesis 11:29)",
        a: "A. Rebekah",
        b: "B. Milcah",
        c: "C. Sarai",
        d: "D. Esther",
        correctAnswer: "C. Sarai"
    },
    Q8: {
        question: "How many of each animal did Noah put on the ark?",
        a: "A. 6",
        b: "B. 2",
        c: "C. 15",
        d: "D. 100",
        correctAnswer: "B. 2"
    },
    Q9: {
        question: "What was the name of the giant who David fought?",
        a: "A. Harris",
        b: "B. Bartholomew",
        c: "C. Fredrick",
        d: "D. Goliath",
        correctAnswer: "D. Goliath"
    },
    Q10: {
        question: "When Moses got older, what did he tell Pharaoh?",
        a: "A. to run away from Egypt and never return",
        b: "B. that they were brothers ",
        c: "C. to let his people go free from slavery",
        d: "D. that he should make Moses his right-hand man",
        correctAnswer: "C. to let his people go free from slavery"
    }
}